<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<articles>
  <article>
    <caption>Electrical safety regulations for the operation of the brewery</caption>
    <desc>The brewery is a 380 volt high-power electrical industrial equipment that poses a threat to human life and health. The brewery also operates in a humid environment, which increases the risk of electric shock. Therefore, it is necessary to strictly observe the safety rules during the operation and maintenance of equipment. The brewery {model} should be connected to 380 volt industrial frequency AC mains. The body of the brewery, as well as the metal piping of hot and cold water and steam pipelines must be grounded with a conductor with a cross section of at least 10 sq. Mm. Grounding conductors must be connected at two points, one of which is on the boiler body, and the second on the cold or hot water pipe outside the cooking room and no closer than 5 m from the first point. The installation must be connected to the network through a residual current device or through a 25 amp three-phase differential circuit breaker.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Rules for the safe use of steam and glycol shirts</caption>
    <desc>Boiler shirts are pressurized to 0.5 bar and operate at temperatures up to 110 degrees C. During operation, do not touch heated surfaces without protective equipment in order to avoid burns, prevent heating in the absence of liquid in the boiler, and do not place parts under voltage (control unit, power wires) near water sources, operate in a ventilated room, avoid humidity in the room at which condensation starts to fall, do not place on uneven, unstable surfaces, observe safety measures when working with heating appliances. Steam-water shirts are under pressure up to 0.5 bar, equipped with a safety valve (operating both for overpressure and for discharge), during operation it is necessary to monitor the pressure to prevent exceeding the specified thresholds. The temperature of the coolant of steam-water and glycol jackets can reach 110 degrees C. When opening the taps of the shirt, it is necessary to use protective gloves made of thick cloth and be out of the line of discharge of steam or liquid.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Brewery Embedded Security {model}</caption>
    <desc>Safety, reliability, safety margin are the most important requirements that we adhere to when designing and manufacturing our equipment. Mechanical safety is implemented by the following elements and procedures: double pressure testing of tanks, valves for vacuum and overpressure, mechanical pressure gauges, end sensors, several thermistors for temperature control, bimetal dial thermometer. Electrical safety includes: grounding, differential machines, compensation for surges and voltage drops, high-quality electronic components, modular design of automation. Algorithmic security includes: automatic stopping during errors and timeouts, logging of all system parameters and operator actions, fault-tolerant execution, automatic recovery after a power outage, the possibility of manual control. At the production stage, only high-quality argon welding is used with professional equipment for quality control of welds.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Preparing the brewery for work</caption>
    <desc>Before starting work, be sure to check the correct operation of the valves of the boiler jackets, check the integrity and appearance of the connectors of the heating elements, make sure that all contacts are clean and dry without scale and oxides, make sure the power cord and fluid supply pipes are intact. check the tightness of the boiler hatch, make sure that there is no liquid on the floor and that all the electric components of the brewery are at a safe distance from the water supply and combustible materials, make sure that all the water supply pipes are tightly connected to the equipment and pumps and fixed. Before starting work, make sure that the shirts have propylene glycol. Set the date and time at the brewery.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Recipe chain selection</caption>
    <desc>Brewery {model} is a model with two active boilers, which allows up to 4 brews per shift due to the simultaneous operation of both boilers. When using a boiler with a supply of hot water and a separate standing whirlpool, it becomes possible to perform up to 6 brews of beer per shift due to the acceleration of the heating phases and faster release of the digester at the stage of virulence. The Ceres software is designed to fulfill the chains of recipes that are set in the corresponding section of the software. Both repeated cooking of one recipe and successive cooking of various recipes are possible. Thus, when the brewery with two active boilers is actively loaded, two recipes are simultaneously executed on the equipment. When cooking parallel recipes, the system automatically synchronizes the speed to avoid violation of prescription algorithms (exceeding mash or cooking pauses). Parameters of timeouts, time tolerances, wort overflow time between boilers are set in the parameters section. When selecting recipes, a color map of the execution and estimated time points are displayed when operator intervention is necessary.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Create, edit, import recipes</caption>
    <desc>Creating or editing recipes comes from the section with a list of recipes. Importing a recipe from the BeerSmith package is done in the recipe editing window from the root directory of USB drives, which can be connected at the back of the brewery control unit. In the recipe settings window, you need to set the basic volumes of the recipe, the mass of the ingredients, and the water parameters. For the mash stage, the temperatures and durations of mash pauses are indicated. If the operator message text is set for a pause, the system will give an audible (optional) and text notification for the operator and begin to count the pause only after the operator completes the action. At the brewing stage, temporary pauses mean the intervals between hops and other additives. The recipe editing window has a convenient menu for editing mash or cooking steps of the recipe.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Standard brewing procedure for brewery {model}</caption>
    <desc>The standard sequence of actions includes preparing the brewery for work, checking the parameters of the recipes, selecting the chain of recipes, starting the process and following the instructions of the automatics (pouring water, loading different batches of malt, pouring into the digester, hop loading), completing the brewing, cleaning and shutting down equipment</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Washing and disinfection</caption>
    <desc>There are two types of washing - washing and disinfecting the inside of boilers and pipelines and washing the outside of the brewery using high-pressure units. To wash the internal surfaces, the boilers themselves are used to heat the flushing solutions, and the circulation pumps - to create a cleaning fluid flow. Flushing of internal cavities is carried out in the manual control mode of the brewery by setting the power of the heating elements. Before cleaning the brewery body with a high-pressure washer, completely disconnect the installation. It is strictly forbidden to wash the automation unit in a high-pressure cleaner to prevent water from entering the power electronics. In case of contamination, disconnect the entire installation and wipe the case with slightly damp rags.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Brewery Maintenance Schedule</caption>
    <desc>Maintenance of the brewery consists in regular inspection of all work units for serviceability and integrity. Particular attention should be paid to the search for violations of the tightness of heating jackets, the integrity of the body of the product, and other electrical equipment, insulation of electrical wiring, and grounding reliability. Shift maintenance should be carried out by maintenance personnel and includes: regular external inspection, cleaning and wiping of housings and working devices, checking the availability and serviceability of grounding, and monitoring the tightness of heating jackets. At least once every three months, it is necessary to check the condition of the wiring and the control system for external damage. At least once a year, places for grounding bolts are cleaned to a shine and coated with TsIATIM-201 grease according to GOST 6267-74.
Every three months, it is necessary to check the tightness of the threaded connections (tighten if loosened). When working with detergents and disinfectants, care must be taken to use rubber gloves and follow the instructions.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Working with the cookbook archive</caption>
    <desc>The brewery’s archive allows you to view the brewing history using a convenient calendar and process schedule. The graph shows the main parameters of the equipment - temperature, power of heating elements, the operation of actuators.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Connect mobile apps</caption>
    <desc>To connect the mobile application for remote monitoring of the brewery, you must enable remote monitoring of the brewery in the settings of the equipment itself, set an access password, and also connect the brewery to a wireless network with Internet access. In the mobile application, you must enter the brewery serial number and access password. Alternatively, you can scan the serial number at the brewery and confirm permission to connect a mobile device.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Failure Actions</caption>
    <desc>The brewery {model} is made with a certain margin of resistance to failures. In the event of a failure in the power supply of the brewery, work will be resumed from the moment of interruption, if the break did not exceed the threshold value of the time duration, which is set in the settings. If the time threshold is exceeded, the recipe will be completed. If the running parallel recipes (or one recipe) were interrupted without the possibility of renewal for any other reasons, then it is possible to complete the cooking in manual mode to avoid product loss. To do this, open both recipes and write down the necessary steps, then open the history section and determine at which step each of the recipes was interrupted. Then, in the recipe window, make a duplicate of the recipe from the mash pot, then edit it by deleting the steps that have been taken. And run the recipe for execution. Bring the recipe in the mash boiler to the end in manual mode by adjusting the boiling power of the power buttons and loading the hops and other ingredients according to the time count that you will conduct yourself.</desc>
  </article>
  <article>
    <caption>Installation and installation rules for the brewery {model}</caption>
    <desc>Boilers must be installed on a non-combustible surface and should be leveled horizontally using adjustable legs. Ground must be connected in accordance with electrical safety requirements. The electrical parts of the equipment must be at least 100 mm above the floor surface. The distance from the walls to the boilers is no closer than 600 mm, provided that the wall is made of non-combustible material. Mini-breweries can be located in single-storey, multi-storey, basement and semi-basement rooms. Production belongs to the category "D": not fire and not explosive. For domestic and warehouse premises, existing areas and domestic services are used. In technological rooms, the walls should be finished with ceramic tiles to a height of 2.0 m. The floors can be made of ceramic tiles or reinforced concrete with a synthetic coating (varnish, enamel, resin), equipped with drainage channels and drains for draining. Wastewater is discharged into an existing sewer. The cooking room must be equipped with: ventilation, with exhaust hoods above the equipment, heating, water supply, water treatment system, power supply according to energy consumption, size not less than 35 sq. M, ceiling height not less than 3 m.
The fermentation room should be equipped with: electrical supply, according to energy consumption, thermal insulation, ventilation, not less than 45 square meters, ceiling height not less than 3.5 m.
Power is supplied from a three-phase network. To reduce the load on one phase, the heating elements are distributed in different phases.
To avoid contamination: the surfaces should be easy to clean and the room should be equipped with a bactericidal air recirculator or UV disinfector.
The malt storage and crushing area should be located in a separate, well-ventilated area.</desc>
  </article>
</articles>